SOURENDRA SETHY () Featured

Web Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Solution

Architecture, HTML, CSS, Node JS, React JS, Java Script, Bootstrap, Angular



Current Designation: Web Developer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Aptara New Media Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Web Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application

Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Solution

Architecture, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, ReactJS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Angular

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Innovative Web Developer with 3 years of experience in website design and Web technologies Demonstrated talent for front and back-end web development to optimize online presence. Seasoned expert in languages such as HTML, CSS and Bootstrap as well as scripting languages JavaScript and Angular Cli.

Work Experience

Aptara New Media as Web Developer

Dec 2017 to Till Date

Consulted with Web Developer to ascertain organizational requirements, then compile, refine and generate webpage roadmap to achieve objectives.

Aptara New Media as Web Developer

Dec 2017 to Dec 2017

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=105dd4a8ddc1cf6f1238f8ced4b1e720095a0c574d460f190b16135f080c...

HTML		
CSS		
JavaScript		
BOOTSTRAP		
angular cli		
SASS		

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
ODIA	Proficient			

Projects

Project Title: IBM Blue Works

Client: Ernst & Young

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jul 2019 - May 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: e-Learning projects for their internal purpose, created in angular cli6 and node js

Project Title: MEDICAL TERMINOLOGY Client: Blue Cross and Blue Shield Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Apr 2018 - Jun 2019

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Created in Angular CLI6 and node js and used MongoDB as database.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General

Countries: India

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Job Type: Permanent